* Platform
* SSL
    * Other Certificates
* Partner
* Support
    * [Resources
        
        Collaterals | FAQ'S](https://emsign.com/resources)
* Sign in
    * Have an account? [Sign in](https://hub.emsign.com/)
    
    * * *
    
    * New to emSign? Create an account to get started.[Sign up](https://hub.emsign.com/enterpriseSignup)
* CUR

Privacy policy
==============

We are sensitive to privacy issues and have established this Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information. This privacy policy should be read in conjunction with our Terms of Service.

We, at emSign, respect your privacy and the confidentiality of your Personal Information. Our company's resources and entire staff are fully committed to safeguarding your personal data i.e email address and other data stored and uploaded in the profile created by you on our website by ensuring that the highest security and other precautionary measures are in place to protect your non-public information which include personally identifiable information except those contained in certificate profiles.

From time to time, emSign may use technologies such as cookies, logs directly or through third party software to automatically collect, store and analyse non-personal information about website user such as IP Address, Browser Type, Referral URL, Clickstream information etc. This information may be used by emSign to put together information about individuals or for reporting on an aggregated basis. emSign intends to use this information to improve emSign's service and experience towards its visitors and customers.

emSign also may be part of various advertising networks to display others ads on our site and use ad-placement software providers to display our ads on others site. These ads may be contextual and may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities and behaviour.

In order to provide good customer experience, emSign collects personal information including Name, Organization, Email Address and other personal information submitted by visitors, clients, subscribers or relying parties to download software, or to submit sales or technical support questions or to seek general information about emSign's products or services.

emSign also collects personal information as outlined in the CP/CPS available at / [http://repository.emSign.com](http://repository.emsign.com/) to issue certificates. Such personal information may also be obtained by emSign from third party data sources for the purpose of validating, confirming or supplementing available customer information. Regardless of the source, emSign treats personal non-public information as confidential information.

emSign may use personal information to market, sell and provide its/Affiliates products and services, offer customer support and renewal services and notify the customer of his order, invoice, payment, revocation, renewal status or other communication via physical or electronic means.

emSign never sells personal information to third parties but may share your information with business partners who are third parties who provide services on our behalf to help with our business activities. All such business partners are required to keep your personal information completely confidential.

emSign routinely reaches out to customers and prospects (who have provided personal information and have not opted out of emSign mailing list) via a number of methods including but not limited to live chat, promotional emails, referral programs. These include the use of third party application vendors or service providers to inform the prospect or customer about a service or product or an order placed with emSign. Such third party provides do not share personally identifiable information about emSign's users with anyone other than emSign. If you receive an unsolicited email related to emSign's products or services and are concerned about your privacy, please forward the entire message and headers (applicable in case of email) to [legal@emSign.com](mailto:legal@emSign.com)

emSign also uses Blogs and Social Media platforms to promote its product or services. You should be aware that your usage of Blogs or Social Media platforms are subject to risks as they are public in nature and any information posted by you there can be read, collected, stored and accessed by other users who access them. To learn how such platforms process your personal information, please read the respective third party application provider's privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our website so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Changes to Our Privacy Statement  
From time to time we may revise this privacy notice. It is your obligation that you visit the website regularly and make yourself aware of any changes we make to this Privacy Statement, including a material change in the way we use your personal information and it will be deemed to be notified to and read by you on your using the Website once we post the same on our Website since the same is available.

Security Measures  
At emSign, we use the industry-standard Secured Socket Layer (SSL) protocol which provides data encryption, message integrity, and server authentication when your data is sent to us. When you see a small lock at the bottom right or left corner of your browser window, you know your data is being encrypted for transmission. All information (including email address) you enter while using emSign is used to provide the services requested by you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information (including email address). All data is stored on emSign servers and is backed up to prevent the loss of data.

While emSign uses industry accepted standards to protect personal information, emSign cannot guarantee absolute security as no method of transmission of data over electronic medium is 100% secure.

Service Alerts and Critical Notices  
Although we respect and honour your privacy preferences, emSign shall maintain the right to contact you when it is required to make you aware of changes (that are of a non-marketing nature), that may impact your ability to use emSign products and services.

Support Section  
[www.emSign.com](http://www.emsign.com/) offers technical support and customer service on the some service plans to our customers. You may choose to submit a question through the support section of the Website or contact our support staff directly. The information submitted via the support section (including email address) is used to research your problem, provide answers, and / or request more information. emSign does retain the right to use your suggestions and product enhancement ideas to improve the Websites and product line without obligation to you. emSign or its business partners are committed to keeping your personal information confidential.

Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose your information (including your email address) as and when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process or other judicial, administrative or investigative proceedings served or initiated on our Website.

IN THE EVENT OF DISCLOSURE OF ANY SUCH INFORMATION FROM THE WEBSITE FOR ANY REASON BEYOND THE CONTROL OF EMSIGN, EMSIGN SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES AND NO ACTION SHALL BE TAKEN AGAINST EMSIGN.

Limitation of Warranties  
Notwithstanding anything to the contrary mentioned herein, the maximum liability that emSign and / or its directors, employees, agents, representatives and authors shall be liable would not exceed the amount paid by you to emSign or as indicated by the contractual agreement between you and emSign. Nothing contained herein shall mean that emSign and / or its directors, employees, agents, representatives and authors shall accept any liability that you or your representatives may notify but in case it is so done, it will be subject to our independent review of the same and our rights of defence. emSign in providing its services makes no warranties of any kind whatsoever. emSign shall have no liability for any errors, malfunctions and /or Loss of data or defects resulting from or related to the use of the information (including software) in the systems used for providing services herein. emSign shall not be liable to you for any indirect, liquidated, special or consequential damages or loss of profits arising from or related to the services provided or the information (including software) used for providing services.

Governing Law and Jurisdiction  
The relationship between you and emSign shall be governed by the Laws of India. You and emSign agree to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located at Bangalore, India.

Certificates
------------

PKI
---

Paperless
---------

Company
-------

Resources
---------

Legal
-----

#### 24X7

#### Mail Us

© eMudhra. All Rights Reserved.
